Yes. Okay. Perfect. But they are not the
same percentages. Correct. J. Correct.
Correct. Correct. And I can go as far as
doing that right
now. But what if we are bullish in what
if we are bullish on the daily and the 4
hour but bearish in the weekly? That's
fine. That's what that's what you
identify these for. We can go on some
examples. I'm done now. So this is what
we have for two, right? There's nothing
else you can type up on two. All right,
cool. You simply now go to the daily. I
mean, there's nothing else you can type
on the weekly. You can't type up because
look, it's very simple. After you
selected this one, can you select any
one of these right here? Is it rejecting
an EMA? No. Okay, next. Is it rejecting
an area of interest on the weekly? No.
Okay, next. Is it rejecting around
psychological level? Yes. But this is
like a daily psychological level, so
we'll save that for them. So,
technically, no. Do we have a weekly
rejection candlestick? No. All right,
cool. We're done on the weekly time
frame. Now we go to the daily. You guys
are seen how simple that is, right? You
guys have seen how we just made that
multiple choice. Fill it in whatever
makes the most sense, right? So the same
thing applies for the daily time frame.
So this is for let's make it for two and
three
weekly time frame.
Yes, rejection candlestick can mean
dogee anything. Yeah, but this this
rejection like is look where price is
right here. If you notice when we go
down to the daily, we are not there.
You're seeing right cuz it's kind of
trading view is like a little like
glitched out or whatever. But it's not
supposed to look like that. But yeah,
it's just cuz trading glitches out. So
this is a side note for the weekly and
then it's going to be the exact same
side note for the daily time frame.
daily time frame and the numbers can go
from
three to
five. You guys are seeing that, right?
Very simple, clean. So, now we'll go to
the daily time frame. What can we type
up from the daily time frame? This is
all like we're not making anything up.
We're just got to we all we have to do
is pick one of these. What do we have on
the daily time
frame? Just hype it up. What do we
have?
Okay.
Okay. Perfect. Okay. So, we have a
daily rejection
candle. As you can see, it's right here.
So this one is already checked off. Bet.
All right. What's next? Do we have
anything
else? Well, we have a round
psychological level. So we have
rejection from daily
round psych level. All right,
cool. So this is now checked off. Oh,
wait. It was like this and then it was
like this. Okay. What else? We have
rejection
from daily area of interest. Now we got
this one checked off. There's no
rejection from an EMA. As you can see,
the EMA is up here. And we're
technically rejecting a structure point,
but it's not the previous structure
point. It's just the It's just our area
of interest. You guys are seeing how of
that. Clean. Perfect. We just checked
everything off. These two other ones,
they don't apply in this example. You
guys are seeing that, right? Type one if
it if it makes
sense.
Perfect. So, when it comes to the
structure point, like if you if you
notice here on the weekly, it's
retesting. For example, this is what I
mean when you're retesting the last
structure point. When it comes like this
and it retests the last structure point.
This is literally the last structure
point. The last structure point. The
last structure point. But if this has an
area of interest here and there's like
whatever like resistance throughout here
and you obviously mark it off as a level
of resistance, it's not Oh, I mean right
here. It's not retesting the last
structure point. It's, you get me? It's
just retesting this resistance here.
Does that make sense? When I mean
retesting structure point, I mean that
it's retesting the last structure point.
If you notice, this is the last
structure point. If you notice right
here, when this does a high, retesting
the last structure point. This retested
the last structure point, but then it
kept going down. So, here for daily time
frame, it's not retesting the last
structure point. This would have been
the last structure
point or
whatever. Is that clear? We can move
on. Okay, perfect. So, this is a side
note. We only buy at a weekly or daily
area of interest. Side note for the
numbers two to three on the weekly time
frame. If we're not rejecting from any
one of these like this is our category
to select in here. Same thing for the
daily time frame. So now that we've
understood this from the daily time
frame,
now we
mandatory need to buy at a
4hour higher low or
potential higher
low at the
shift of
structure with a angul.
golfing. I found
golfing. Okay, this is literally it,
guys. This is literally the whole entire
strategy in these five boxes right here.
And you guys are going to see how simple
it
gets with the side notes. It makes a lot
more sense. I agree. My bad. You know,
now I know. Now at this point, I just do
this and that's it. You know, [\h__\h] you
know, trust me. I wish I would have done
this at the beginning. It's a lot easier
to understand it like this, but you
know, like it I don't know why. I mean,
now I just I don't know. All right. So,
this is where after we identify
everything. So, as of right now, we are
we've checked both of these boxes off.
Now we're on to our next box. These side
notes are next level. Yeah, they're very
simple. I just did this in like two
seconds. Like I'm telling you, it's very
simple cuz like when I say it, I'm
talking a lot of [\h__\h] So you guys can
probably get confused and like the words
get lost. But when I type it up, it it's
literally like right there. So now we
are done with this box, right? So now we
go on to our next box. You guys get
that? You guys are with me on that? Type
one of it if it makes
sense. Perfect. Okay, cool.
Okay. So, now this is where we're going
to go down to, but let's do this. See,
bro, I'm getting more creative with this
[\h__\h] Box one. So, we know this is one,
two, three. There's impossible to to
like get
lost. Box
two. Box three. Right. So, now we're on
box three. Yeah. step one, two, and
three. That's literally it. There's
three steps to it. So now we go down to
the 4 hour. So now on the 4 hour, we
need whatever it says right here. We
need a higher low to buy. We need a
mander low on the 4 hour or potential
higher on the shift structure. So now
this is just for cells. We
need mandatory need
a sell at
a 4hour lower high or
[Music]
potential lower high at the shift of
structure with a
engulfing
at resistance.
last
support. So, this is the same exact
thing, just bearish, right? You guys are
seeing what I did there. Like, this is
obviously if we're having a higher low
and then this is if we're having a lower
high, right? Simple. I just did that to
kind of have that
lens. Do you always buy after a higher
low on the 4 hour or not? Do you always
buy after? I don't get what you mean.
um by that. All right, cool. So, as of
right now, there's number
six, waiting for higher or potential
high. Does that make any sense what
number six is? Is it
clear? Type one. Type just type
one. Okay, perfect. So now the ideal
trade setup here is waiting for this to
come here and go like this or have this
come here and then do this because then
this 4 hour will shift bullish. So this
4 hour will then be
bullish giving us a 20% confluence here
because then we have the weekly and then
the 4hour bullish. Right? This is the
ideal trade setup. But if you notice, we
can take a trade at a
potential higher low. What is a
potential higher low? Exactly what would
happen here. This comes into this area,
which is again the round psychological
13,800 daily area of interest. And it
has to create this fluctuation in order
to have the push out. this just can't
get out of here for no reason. Like it
needs to have this retracement to have
the push to then do this. You get me?
But again, this is something that you
will learn on your own as you continue
to trade. I'm setting the wave, setting
the example of how it has to happen in
order for it to happen. And like I
explained to you guys, I personally
myself, I would have gotten in right
here if I was actively watching the
market. But like you guys said, the 4
hour is still bearish. Yes, I agree. But
then keep in mind, in order for this to
have a higher high, like it's got to
create the higher low
before you guys listen to what I said.
Like in order for this to have the
higher high, it has to create a higher
low. So, this is where I would have
gotten in. But again, it comes with a
little bit more experience. You guys
will get it over time. But for this
example, we're going to keep it strictly
to the strategy exactly what we've been
waiting for. Um, like I I can go on the
example where I would have gotten in
right here. So, if you notice, if you go
down to the 30 minute time frame, we
would have waited for the shift to the
structure to go bullish right here.
Bullish engulfing on the 30 minute.
Bullish engulfing on the one hour.
Bullish engulfing on the 2 hour. Morning
star. Bullish engulfing on the 4 hour.
This is your trade right here for your
stop loss under this zone. So this is uh
52 pips. Add five. So like 57. I would
have probably done 60 pips. And then my
take profit is my daily structure point.
But we'll get to that very soon. But for
this example, we'll keep it to exactly
what we were waiting for. We're waiting
for a higher low. Let's not put
potential. You'll know your own higher
low soon, right? You guys are with me so
far. I just kind of went like on a
little rant there, but we're still
waiting for the same thing. You guys are
with
me? Let's type one if you guys are with
me. Okay. So, as of right now, we're
still waiting for a higher low. Why?
Because what do we have? We have a
higher high.
After this higher high, we now need a
higher low. Again, we don't know when
this push is going to stop. It could
stop here, here, here, here, here, or it
can legit never stop. It can do exactly
what it did here, here, when we broke
above this structure point. We wanted a
higher low to go long. Never happened.
It just kept going. It's not our trade.
Literally, there's nothing we can do.
There's no strategy that I know how to
trade to catch this move. So, we're
gonna stick to what we know. And it's
waiting for a higher low. So, let's just
keep it going. Oh [\h__\h] this looks like
it can start the higher low move. This
is where we go down to the 30 minute
time frame or 1 hour time frame or
whatever. Right.
So, after I'm getting crazy with these
boxes, so let's see.
How do you spell like moderating
moderating?
Whatever. Let's see
if I spelled this so wrong. Siri can't
even fix
it. Moderating. All right, we're in
constant mo. Thank you guys. We're in
constant moderating of
the 15
minute of
the 15 m 30
and 1
hour shift of
structure to
continue with the higher to Continue.